thegrocerygame.com 2015-12-06

# Security Information - Privacy Statement - The Grocery Game

Thank you for visiting TheGroceryGame.com, a Grocery Game, Inc. site.

Your privacy is important to us, and we are committed to protecting the personal information you choose to share with us. This Privacy Policy applies to our Website. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, protect, and share information on our Website. This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information preferences.

WHEN YOU USE OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND THE GROCERY GAME WILL HAVE THE RIGHT TO USE YOUR INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO HAVE YOUR INFORMATION USED IN ANY OF THE WAYS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE OUR WEBSITE.

WHEN YOU USE OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND INTERMARKETS WILL HAVE THE RIGHT TO USE YOUR INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO HAVE YOUR INFORMATION USED IN ANY OF THE WAYS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE OUR WEBSITE.

##  Information We Collect through the Site

**Personally Identifiable Information:** We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, username, email address, credit card details, and other information as we may from time to time request from you (“Personally Identifiable Information”) if you share such information with us. For example, you may be asked to provide us with certain Personally Identifiable Information when you register with or use our services, when you register with or use the Site, or at any time we provide an online form. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register with or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain content, features, or services available on or through the Site.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** We automatically collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information when you use the Site. Non-Personally Identifiable Information includes demographic information (such as age, gender, city or state) and a user’s click stream information (i.e., web pages viewed, the date and time at which those pages were viewed and interaction with content and advertisements on those Web pages).

**Cookies and Web Beacons:** We may use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser), Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a website that monitors usage), and other similar technologies to improve the quality of the Site. Our cookies and web beacons are used for web server statistics only and does not include your name or anything identifiable to you.

Cookie Opt Out: With respect to Gourmet Ads, the primary ad server is Appnexus and you can opt out of cookies from them by visiting:

<http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy> and Opting Out.

You can also opt out of cookies using the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at this page:

<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

Finally, you can choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.

##  How We Use and Share Information Collected through the Site

**General:** We use Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information for internal purposes only, such as to notify you of new products or services, to send service notifications, to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve the Site, to conduct research, to solicit your feedback and input about the Site, and to offer e-mail promotions from our trusted network of partners (which you may opt-out of at any time, as described more fully below). Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information may be combined with data collected from other sources, consistent with applicable law, so that we may further improve the relevance and effectiveness of products, services, and advertisements offered on or through the Site.

**Service Providers:** The Grocery Game may share Personally Identifiable Information with its service providers that help us provide the services that you request (“Service Providers”). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as credit card processing, advertising, analytics tools, data management services, Web hosting, and Web development. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services, however, each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved in order to protect your information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information Only:** We use this information to help us understand how people use our Site. For example, each time you use the Site we automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your ISP, which pages you view, and the time and duration of your visits to the Site.

**Other Transfers:** We may share Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with The Grocery Game.  If The Grocery Game is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we may disclose or transfer Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information in connection with such transaction. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Sharing:** The Grocery Game may use, and disclose to third parties, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information regarding the Site (e.g., number of visits, page views, and the like) without your permission. However, such information does not identify you individually. As for Personally Identifiable Information, we may share your first name, email address, zip code, and party affiliation with our trusted network of partners. However, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of sharing such information.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement:** The Grocery Game cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. The Grocery Game reserves the right to disclose Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of The Grocery Game or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

##  Opt-Out Procedure

**Opt-Out of Third Party Sharing of Personal Information:** If you do not want to receive email promotions from our trusted network of partners, email us at [unsubscribe@thegrocerygame.com](mailto:unsubscribe@thegrocerygame.com) and you will be removed from our Third Party disclosure list.

Once a request to opt out has been received, The Grocery Game will send a confirming email message to the user that the user’s Personally Identifiable Information has been successfully opted out of The Grocery Game database. If you do not receive this confirmatory email, then please contact us to ensure that your request was received and processed.

##  Third Party Websites

The Site may contain links to websites or content operated and maintained by third parties. The Grocery Game  does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our practices. If you click on a link or an advertisement, the privacy policy of the website to which you link will govern the collection and use of your information by that website’s operator(s). You access such third-party websites or content at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before disclosing any information to the website. For more information, please click here.

##  Security

We recognize the importance of safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. Accordingly, we employ standard security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect any information you transmit on or through the Site, please be advised that The Grocery Game assumes no responsibility or liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access, or other causes beyond The Grocery Game's reasonable control.

##  Processing in the United States

We process and store all information in the United States. By using our Site, you agree that the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personally Identifiable Information will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.

##  Children's Privacy Statement

The Grocery Game  Site is directed to, and intended for use by, adults only. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. Because we do not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

##  Privacy Policy Changes

The Grocery Game  may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you should review this Policy periodically. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Those changes will go into effect on the Revision Date shown at the top of the revised Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

##  Questions and Concerns

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [marketing@thegrocerygame.com](mailto:marketing@thegrocerygame.com) or send us a letter at The Grocery Game, Inc., Attention: 9720 Wilshire Blvd, 6th Floor, Beverly Hills, CA  90212

##  California Privacy Notice

California's Shine the Light law provides California residents with the right to receive disclosures about any sharing of their personal information with other companies.

If you are a California resident and you provided your personal information to The Grocery Game, then, once each calendar year, you may submit a written request for information about the information we shared, if any, with other companies for their use in direct marketing. To submit your written request, please email us at [marketing@thegrocerygame.com](mailto:marketing@thegrocerygame.com) or send us a letter at The Grocery Game, Attention: Privacy, 9720 Wilshire Blvd, 6th Floor, Beverly Hills, CA 90212 with "Request for California Privacy" in the letter subject line.

Within 30 days of receiving your request, we will send you a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties.

We reserve our right not to respond to requests sent more than once in a calendar year, or requests submitted to an address other than the one posted in this notice.

Please note that the California Shine the Light law does not cover all information sharing. Our disclosure only includes information covered by the law.

The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on or about June 18, 2013

## Save 67% or more on groceries by joining The Grocery Game

Enter your zip to find out which stores are available.  
ZIP CODENEXT 

  * 10,399

###### Deals Valid Today in the US

  * 6,239

###### Unadvertised Sales this week

  * 21,863

###### Deals Members Shopped For This Week

  * $76,827

###### Amount Members Saved this week

  * 50

###### Local lists in the US

  * $557,209

###### Amount Members Saved this month

## FOLLOW US

## REFER FRIENDS

Earn $5 account credit for each friend who joins. 

FRIEND'S EMAIL  
  
RULES INVITE

## MORE SAVINGS

© 2015 The Grocery Game, Inc. All rights reserved.
